How could I kill my father?
Zhang Tianyou!
Tell me!
I didn't kill my father, did I?
You're lying to me.
Zhang Tianyou!
So what if I killed him?
Power and strength are everything!
Lord Evil God!
Give me your power!
Let me be Destined by Fate!
Human greed is indeed scarier than evil creatures.
You're about to die and you still dare to mess with me?
What?
Are you trying to kill me with that hand?
Zhang Tianyou, you're done for.
Go to hell!
Lord Evil God!
Leave my body intact!
Lord Evil God, wait for me!
Zhang Tianyou!
Are you okay?
Brother!
Chief, as you ordered,
the men are waiting outside.
Xiaoshuai, Xiaomei,
have the men take Miss Sheng
and Master Wan back.
Yes.
Be careful, everyone.
Chief Leng,
thank you.
This place hides many ancient viruses.
Let's use explosives to blow it all up.
All this time,
I thought you'd use magic to cleanse the tomb.
Who knew you'd just blow it up in the end.
Let's go.
Blow it up.
Yes.
I knew it.
What I saw just now was all real.
So the treasure is all here.
This treasure brings power and strength.
Zhang Tianyou,
that Day of Reckoning on the full moon...
what was it really about?
The events 20 years ago happened on a full moon.
The so-called Day of Reckoning
was actually first spread by me.
Just to push you to join me down here sooner.
Twenty years ago,
what The Four Great Families did to your people...
But
none of it can be undone.
Dad.
This whole tomb raiding business
is merely driven by greed and obsession,
willingly crossing between life and death.
Back then, my people,
if not for their greed for the treasure in this tomb,
wouldn't have led The Four Great Families here.
Right and wrong
are buried with a shovel of yellow earth,
sealed away here forever.
It's gonna blow! Hurry!
It's all mine.
An illusion.
It must be an illusion.
Don't try to scare me.
Mine.
It's all mine.
All of this...
was due to ancient rotting wood and damp mud
releasing some unknown pathogen.
And then,
it distorted their vision and hearing,
and affected the central nervous system.
You mean the hallucinations they saw,
and The Four Great Families' dream murders,
were all because of this?
Exactly.
Then...
They're here.
Now that the Wan, Mei, Qi, and Sheng families
and the Sand-Turning Gang are now one,
Zhang Tianyou,
you, our Dragon-Seeking Champion,
are going to have your hands full.
Brother Mouse,
I suddenly really miss
our good old days as Diggers.
I don't want to be a Digger again.
Your top priority right now
is to hurry and find a wife to help you.
Did you guys just hear that?
I thought the so-called evil creature back then
was really just a strange genetic disease.
But later on...
Old Zhang,
you were a storyteller before the Liberation, right?
What evil creatures...
and strange diseases...
Just keep making things up.
So many things,
true or false,
whether you believe them or not,
are like opening or closing the door to your heart.
If there were really evil creatures,
wouldn't an anti-aircraft gun blow them to pieces?
An anti-aircraft gun can destroy evil creatures,
but it can't destroy greed, obsession, and lust.
My young friends,
times have changed now.
Any strange disease can be cured.
But since ancient times,
only conscience can restrain greed and obsession.
Old Zhang,
you should just go write a novel.
Your story isn't mysterious enough.
You need to make it more exciting.
By the way,
why do I remember your name is Zhang Shouling?
I'm getting old.
I can't even remember my own name.
Alright.
We're leaving.
Let's go, let's go.
Heading home, heading home.
This Old Zhang.
Tianyou, Shouling.
I can't remember clearly.
I only remember...
Where wind hides and qi gathers, there lie the tombs of emperors and kings.
One shovel opens the boundary of yin and yang; success and failure all lie within the yellow earth.